BRADLEY BENTOW

Student Software Engineer MONTESANO, 98563 (360)584-0037

O DETAILS O

822 E Pioneer Ave, Apt. 311, Montesano, 98563 (360)584-0037 bentow131@gmail.com

o LINKS o

(Github) https://github.com/Belligerent131

(LinkedIn)

https://www.linkedin.com/in/bbentow

o SKILLS o

Full Stack

Web Development

Bootstrap 4

Database Development

Backend Development

PROFILE

A passionate Software Engineer student with several years of personal experience. I have experience in several languages and modern technologies, Including Oracle Cloud Services, Microsoft Azure. Also, full stack applications using React, Redux, and GraphQL.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Field Service Technician at Capital Business Machines, Inc., Olympia, WA

October 2019 — Present

- Converse with customers to determine details of equipment problems.
- Reassemble machines after making repairs or replacing parts.
- Travel to customers' stores or offices to service machines or to provide emergency repair service.
- Install and configure new equipment, including operating software or peripheral equipment.
- Reinstall software programs or adjust settings on existing software to fix machine malfunctions.

Corrections Officer at Washington State Dept. of Corrections, Aberdeen, WA

July 2013 — September 2019

- Assisted with recruitment and training of new employees, while also monitoring the safety of current employees.
- Use weapons, handcuffs, and physical force to maintain discipline and order among prisoners.
- Conduct fire, safety, and sanitation inspections.
- Monitor conduct of prisoners in housing unit, or during work or recreational activities,
 according to established policies, regulations, and procedures, to prevent escape or violence.
- Settle disputes between inmates.

Watercraft Operator at Army Reserves, Tacoma, Wa

February 2008 — February 2016

- Maintain government-issued certifications, as required.
- Steer ships under the direction of commanders or navigating officers or direct helmsmen to steer, following designated courses.
- Progressed to the rank of Specialist (E-4).
- Attended training events in courses pertaining to leadership.
- Handle lines to moor vessels to wharfs, to tie up vessels to other vessels, or to rig towing lines.

Audio Video Installer at Westport Shipyard LLC, Westport, WA

March 2012 — May 2013

- Install equipment and accessories such as stereos, navigation equipment, communication equipment, and security systems.
- Installed in-wall and ceiling speakers for a great surround-sound experience.
- Maintained systems and provided trouble-shooting services when needed.
- Tested systems post-set up to ensure they worked and to make certain customers were comfortable and understood how to operate them.
- Reported all issues to management.

EDUCATION

B.S. Information Technology, Liberty University, Lynchburg, VA

September 2018 — June 2022

- Advance concepts of Object-Oriented Programming
- Adapt and use sever languages such as C#, C++, Python, Javascript, Html, Css.
- Courses oriented towards business organization and leadership.
- SQL and NoSQL databases heavily emphasized towards Oracle systems

COURSES

Warrior Leadership Course, Army Reserves

July 2015 — August 2015

Basic Essential Skills for Instructors, Washington State Dept. of Corrections

February 2017 — February 2017